NUNTAWAT FANGRITLONG



PROFILE

I have experience in System, Network, and Cloud. I have passionate about exploring and introducing new innovations. With a flexible mindset, I'm capable of both conceptualizing network designs and managing cloud infrastructure development and administration.

CONTACT

- **** 080-9746514
- ✓ nuntawat.works@gmail.com
- **356/98** Bangkok,10260

EDUCATION

MAHASARAKHAM UNIVERSITY
 Faculty of Informatics,
 Bachelor ComputerScience

2016 - 2019

INTERNSHIP

CETA TESTSYSTEME GMBH 4 MONTH - 2020

- Configuration Webdav uses a Linux server (Debian)
- Laravel framework and (Firebird SQL)
- Angular framework and use tools (Bootstrap, Bulma, Ngx
- Bootstrap, Angular Material)

SKILLS

- Ansible for server on-prem and AWS cloud
- Squid proxy for internet
- Terraform for AWS cloud
- Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins
- Script Linux, Nginx

SYSTEM CLOUD ENGINEER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cloud Engineer (Minor Project)

FUJITSU (THAILAND) CO., LTD.

- Cloud Skills
- · AWS Cloud:
- Networking: VPC, Subnets, Transit Gateways, VPN
- Computer & Scaling: EC2, Auto Scaling Groups, ALB
- Storage: Amazon S3,
- Automate: Terraform & Ansible To AWS
- GitHub, GitLab (Action) to AWS (Lambda, ECR, ECS)
- Monitoring & Logging: CloudWatch, CloudTrail, Grafana
- Databases: Amazon RDS
- Proxy Solutions: HAProxy, Squid Proxy
- CONTAINER: Docker, ECS (Fargate, EC2)
- Azure Cloud:
- Networking & Compute: vNet, Virtual Machines (VMs),
- Monitoring: Azure Monitor, Metrics
- Automation & Scripting: Azure Automation Account, Azure PowerShell Script
- Identity & Access Management: SAML App Configuration for SSO
- Identity & Access Management. SAME App Configuration for 550
 Hybrid & Migration Solutions: Azure Arc, Azure Site Recovery (ASR), On-Premises to Cloud Migration
- Observability & Logging: Prometheus, Node Exporter, Blackbox Exporter, Loki, Promtail

System & Network Engineer

TRI PETCH IT SOLUTIONS CO. LTD.

2022 - 2023

2024 - CURRENT

- Network
 - Cisco Configuration
 - Switch Cisco, DNA, ISE, WLC, AP
- Windows Server and Linux
 - o Control and config Server
 - VMware ESXi
 - VCenter
 - Monitoring server
 - Security patch for all TPG servers (400 units)
 - Monthly Report
- AD Active Directory
 - Manage user account for all users TPG 13 domain
 - Manage GPO and Policy for TPG
 - o Build script replace manual action over 20 task
- Google
 - Super Admin for Google
- Project
 - o 2 Factor Authentication (2FA) Rublon
 - VA scan
 - Automate report

System & Network Engineer

PRO INSIDE CO. LTD.

- Network Configuration
 - o Switch: Cisco, Huawei
 - Routing, VLAN, Trunk
 - Firewall Configuration:
 - Sopgos xg, Huawei, Fortigate
- System Configuration
 - VMware ESXi, Vcenter
 - Nutanix
 - NVR
 - Storage: Dahua, Huawei, HP
- Open-source Firewall
 - OPNsense:
 - o PfSense:
 - Ipfire:

2021 - 2022